+62895334568841

# **Bachtiar Fatur Rohim**

## **Web Developer**

Fast learning on all aspect of web development including front and backend with 3 years experiences in web programming professionally. Have experience working in national and multinational companies, and accustomed to working on a project base and product base

# **Work Experience**

# MadeIndonesia - Fullstack Wordpress Developer

#### MARCH 2020 - CURRENT

- Become Fullstack Developer and successfully helped develop a small business into a digital business
- Develop more than 20+ projects using custom WordPress CMS, Javascript, CSS/SCSS, PHP
- Create custom plugins to handle complex projects that use Woocommerce and Mollie Payment Gateway
- Slicing a responsive web layout using HTML, CSS/SCSS, and Javascript
- Collaboratively work with the designer team and the project manager from Netherland
- Accustomed to leading projects with the frontend team
- Manage standardized coding for the developer team
- Deploy a final product to the server using FTP and Gitlab CI/CD

# CronosERP - Backend Developer (Laravel)

# AUGUST 2019 - MARCH 2020,

- Develop an ERP system using Laravel Framework
- Develop a 'Scrap Modules' features
- Mapping the relationships between databases and designing a more efficient system flow
- Create an interactive user interface using JavaScript and Jquery
- Work collaboratively with other divisions such as Finance and
- Working with multiple database technology such MySQL and PostgreSQL

### sistemtoko.com - Web Developer Internship

#### INTERNSHIP | JUNE 2019 - AUGUST 2019.

- Create a full E-Commerce application, starting from the database design, to becoming a complete application
- Develop a bunch of applications using Laravel, Codelgniter, and ReactJS

### Freelance

#### SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

As a self-employed entrepreneur, I help clients with their cool idea into an interactive and solid web application. I mostly use Laravel Framework on my freelance project.

### **Education**

# University of Technology Yogyakarta

### 2017 - 2022 BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN INFORMATION SYSTEMS

Learn more in the world of programming starting from basic algorithms to advanced ones using C++ and Java until be interested in web development, in the second semester deepening the world of web development using html, css and javascript. I lead a final project to finish the last semester and build HRMS to fulfill my final project in college. I took a semester leaves in my 5th semester and use it for working full-time as a web developer and continue my study on the next year while working fulltime, but I still have a good GPA score tho'.

GPA: 3.64

# SMA Negri 6 Cirebon

2015 - 2017

Get to know and interest the world of programming and start learning html self-taught

## **Skills**

Soft skills: Leadership • Problem Solving • Curious, eager to learn • Critical Thinking

Hard skills: PHP, Go, Javascript, jQuery, CSS/SCSS, HTML, WordPress, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Laravel, Vuejs, ReactJS, Git, Docker

Language: Bahasa (native) • English

#### Contact:



gitlab.com/MI-Bachtiar



https://www.linkedin.com/in/bachtiar-fatur-rohim-589478185/



# YAYASAN DHARMA BHAKTI IPTEK

# UNIVERSITAS TEKNOLOGI YOGYAKARTA

ol. Siliwangi (Ringroad Utara), Jombor, Sleman, Yogyakarta. Telp: +62-274-623310 Fax: +62-274-623306. Website: http://www.uty.ac.id E-mail: info@uty.ac.id

### TRANSKRIP AKADEMIK

Nomor Seri : 00207/P.DIPLOMA-UTY/TRA-SI-Diploma-Tiga/V/2022

Nomor Ijazah Nasional

: 574032022000026

Nomor Pokok Mahasiswa

: 3173111012

Nama Mahasiswa

: BACHTIAR FATUR ROHIM

Tempat, Tanggal Lahir

: CIREBON, 18 SEPTEMBER 1999

Program Studi

: SISTEM INFORMASI

Program

: DIPLOMA TIGA

Tanggal Lulus

: 1 APRIL 2022

Predikat Kelulusan : PUJIAN

Mata Kuliah	SKS	Nilai	Mata Kuliah	SKS	Nilai
AGAMA ISLAM	2	Α	PEMROGRAMAN WEB I PRAKTIK	2	Α
ALGORITMA DAN STRUKTUR DATA I	2	В	PERANCANGAN BASIS DATA	2	В
ALGORITMA DAN STRUKTUR DATA I PRAKTIK	1	В	PERANCANGAN BASIS DATA PRAKTIK	1	В
ALJABAR VEKTOR DAN MATRIKS	2	В	SISTEM MANAJEMEN BASISDATA I	2	В
APLIKASI TEKNOLOGI INFORMASI I	2	A	SISTEM MANAJEMEN BASISDATA I PRAKTIK	2	A
BAHASA INDONESIA	2	A	APLIKASI PERANGKAT BERGERAK I	2	A
DASAR AKUNTANSI	3	A	APLIKASI PERANGKAT BERGERAK I PRAKTIK	2	A
INTEGRATED ENGLISH	2	В	DESAIN ANTAR MUKA SISTEM INFORMASI	2	Α
KEWARGANEGARAAN	2	A	PEMROGRAMAN WEB II	2	Α
SISTEM OPERASI	2	A	PEMROGRAMAN WEB II PRAKTIK	2	Α
SISTEM OPERASI PRAKTIK	1	A	PERANCANGAN SISTEM BERORIENTASI OBJEK	3	Α
ALGORITMA DAN STRUKTUR DATA II	2	A	SISTEM INFORMASI AKUNTANSI	2	A
ALGORITMA DAN STRUKTUR DATA II PRAKTIK	1	A	SISTEM MANAJEMEN BASISDATA II	2	Α
APLIKASI TEKNOLOGI INFORMASI II	2	A	SISTEM MANAJEMEN BASISDATA II PRAKTIK	2	Α
COMMUNICATIVE ENGLISH	2	A	SOFTWARE BERBASIS LAYANAN	2	В
DESAIN WEB	2	A	APLIKASI PERANGKAT BERGERAK II	2	В
DESAIN WEB PRAKTIK	2	Α	APLIKASI PERANGKAT BERGERAK II PRAKTIK	2	A
ETIKA PROFESI	2	В	ENGLISH FOR PRESENTATION	2	Α
JARINGAN DAN INSTALASI KOMPUTER	2	A	KEWIRAUSAHAAN	3	Α
JARINGAN DAN INSTALASI KOMPUTER PRAKTIK	1	A	METODOLOGI PENELITIAN	2	Α
KONSEP SISTEM INFORMASI	3	A	PEMROGRAMAN WEB BERBASIS FRAMEWORK	2	Α
STATISTIKA	2	В	PEMROGRAMAN WEB BERBASIS FRAMEWORK PRAKTIK	2	Α
ANALISA DAN PERANCANGAN SISTEM INFORMASI	3	A	PENGEMBANGAN KEPRIBADIAN	2	Α
PANCASILA	2	A	SISTEM INFORMASI BERBASIS WEB	2	В
PEMROGRAMAN BERORIENTASI OBYEK	2	A	SISTEM INFORMASI BERBASIS WEB PRAKTIK	2	A
PEMROGRAMAN BERORIENTASI OBYEK PRAKTIK	2	В	INOVASI SISTEM INFORMASI & TEKNOLOGI MODERN	2	В
PEMROGRAMAN WEB I	2	В	TUGAS AKHIR	6	C

SKS Kumulatif

:112

IP Kumulatif : 3,64

:Implementasi Human Resource Management System Berbasis Web (Studi Judul Tugas Akhir Kasus: Software House Born Digital Yogyakarta)



Yogyakarta, 25 Mei 2022 rektur,

am Diploma

arman, S.Kom., M.Kom., Ph.D.

NIK: 11 0900 034



# Sertifikat

# Intensive Bootcamp Backend Development with Go

Diberikan kepada

# **Bachtiar Fatur Rohim**

Atas partisipasinya sebagai **Peserta** dengan predikat **COMPLETION** dalam *Intensive*Bootcamp Development with Go pada tanggal 6-29 Juni 2022.

Yogyakarta, 08 Juli 2022





# **CERTIFICATE**

**OF APPRECIATION** 

IS PROUDLY PRESENTED TO

# **Bachtiar Fatur Rohim**

Telah mengikuti program kursuscoding.com selama 1.5 bulan penuh untuk belajar Php, Mysql, Bootstrap, Jquery, Laravel, Codeigniter, ReactJs. Dinyatakan lulus dengan baik, dan diyakini sudah siap untuk menempuh dunia peker

25.7.2019

DATE



Dodi Prakoso

**MENTOR** 

2/19/2021 View Transcript



# Authenticated Digital Transcript of Certifications

Bachtiar Fatur Rohim Kampus 1 Universitas Teknologi Yogyakarta jin siliwangi Jombor sleman yogyakarta Yogyakarta 55285 dorayakimoo9@gmail.com

This real-time Certiport Digital Transcript is derived from a global database which tracks and authenticates certification exams administered by over 12,000 testing centers worldwide.

#### MICROSOFT OFFICE SPECIALIST

#### Certifications

Microsoft Office Word 2013

Granted



#### **Exams**

77-418: MOS: Microsoft Office Word 2013 Administered by: Universitas Teknologi Yogyakarta - PUSKOM Language: English

5/25/2018 Passed

For information about Certiport, please visit www.certiport.com. Certiport is the leading provider of global, performance-based certification programs and services designed to enable individual success and lifetime advancement through certification.